{
    "subject": "resource/Quetzal_(band)",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Quetzal (band) is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9601683616638184,
            "question": "Is the band Quetzal American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.951688289642334,
            "question": "Is Quetzal a US-based band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8681377172470093,
            "question": "Where is the band Quetzal from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8189013600349426,
            "question": "Which country are Quetzal musicians from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7374374270439148,
            "question": "What is the nationality of the band members in Quetzal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7255247831344604,
            "question": "What country is the band Quetzal based in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.659529983997345,
            "question": "Where did Quetzal originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6502269506454468,
            "question": "In what nation did the band Quetzal form?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5948927998542786,
            "question": "What is the origin country of Quetzal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5285640358924866,
            "question": "To which country does Quetzal belong?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Quetzal (band) is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9145_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the origin country of Quetzal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9145_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what nation did the band Quetzal form?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9145_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Quetzal originate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9145_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9145_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9145_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9145_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9145_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9145_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9145_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9145_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9145_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9145_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9145_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the text states they are an \"East LA Chican@ rock group\" and  mentions their performance at Reston Community Center in Virginia, it does not explicitly state their nationality. However, the fact that they are a band playing music within the US strongly implies they are from the United States.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Quetzal is a bilingual Chicano rock band from East Los Angeles, California. While it is mentioned as being part of the US music scene and winning a Grammy award in the context of an American festival, there is no specific information about their international touring or recognition outside of the USA to definitively say they are \"from\" the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Quetzal (band) is from United States.\" Specifically, they mention that Quetzal is an East Los Angeles band and that several of its members are associated with the University of North Texas College Of Music in Denton, Texas."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "the band's name \"Quetzal\" originates from Mexican culture (son jarocho) and they play a mix of Mexican rhythms, Chicano rock, Afro-Cuban music, etc., which suggests that their musical roots are more closely tied to Mexico than the United States.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}